<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FlappyBird</string>
    <string name="aboutText">Nowadays, the rules of the game involve two teams of six or ten people competing. Their task, as before, is to get the ball into the opponents\' goal. To do this, they use a special stick. In the lacrosse terminology it is referred to as a stick. Its striking part, called the head, is equipped with a net. It helps the player catch the ball and hold it. The lacrosse ball also has its own features. Its diameter is 63–65 mm and its weight is 140-147 g. The coating material is rubber. The color does not matter, but traditionally it is white. So the ball is easier to see on the green field. The team is conventionally divided into four types of players: forwards and defenders, midfielders and goalkeeper. Each has its own zone on the field. Only midfielders are allowed to play in any, taking on the role of striker or defender. At high level clubs, midfielders are divided into attacking and defending midfielders. The contest is judged by three referees at once. Lacrosse strategy is similar to other team competitions. Players pass to each other. The goal of the defender is to prevent the opponent from scoring. It is allowed to kick the ball with the stick and push each other in the body. For safety, players wear a helmet</string>
    <string name="russianText">В настоящее время правила игры предполагают соревнование двух команд из шести или десяти человек. Их задачей, как и прежде, является завести мяч в ворота соперников. Для этого используют специальную клюшку. В терминологии лакросса она значится как стик. Его ударная часть, называемая головой, снабжена сеткой. Она помогает игроку поймать мяч и удержать его. Мяч для лакросса также имеет свои особенности. Диаметр его составляет 63-65 мм, а вес – 140-147 г. Материалом покрытия является резина. Цвет не имеет значения, но традиционно это белый. Так мяч легче увидеть на зеленом поле. Команда условно разделена на четыре типа игроков: нападающих и защитников, полузащитников и вратаря. У каждого есть своя зона на поле. Только полузащитникам разрешено играть в любой, взяв на себя роль нападающего или защитника. В клубах высокого уровня полузащитников делят на атакующих и защищающих. Судят состязание сразу трое судей. Стратегия лакросса напоминает другие командные соревнования. Игроки передают друг другу пасы. Цель защитника – предотвратить гол противника. Разрешается выбивать мяч стиком и толкать друг друга в тело. С целью безопасности игроки надевают шлем</string>
    <string name="language">LANGUAGE</string>
    <string name="russianlanguage">ЯЗЫК</string>
    <string name="vibration">VIBRATION</string>
    <string name="russianVibration">ВИБРАЦИЯ</string>
</resources>